<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Joe Wright&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Joe Wright&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://joewaynewright.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What was the most valuable position in the NBA during the 2019-2020 season?</title>
      <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/post/2021/04/05/what-was-the-most-valuable-position-in-the-nba-during-the-2019-2020-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joewaynewright.github.io/post/2021/04/05/what-was-the-most-valuable-position-in-the-nba-during-the-2019-2020-season/</guid>
      <description>One of the longest held debates amongst NBA fanatics is over which player deserves the Most Valuable Player (MVP) award for each given season. It is a purposefully subjective award that stirs the pot and incites heated arguments between both media members and fans about what value really means in the NBA.
While this debate is a fascinating discussion, I want to look at player value in a broader sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports Data Analysis and Visualization</title>
      <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/post/2021/03/16/sports-data-analysis-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joewaynewright.github.io/post/2021/03/16/sports-data-analysis-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>This is a faux post for my website so I can get the hang of posting blogs! For my big project this semester, I’m interested in finding out what position in the NBA is the most important? I want to analyze which position brings a team the most win shares and which players in said positions are outliers. I’m also interested in finding out which position has the best shooting percentages, turnover ratio and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Joe</title>
      <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joewaynewright.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m an undergraduate student at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln pursuing a double major in Sports Media Communications and Advertising/Public Relations with a minor in political science. I have a varied set of work experiences in the journalism field working for national sports networks as well as writing for a major local and university newspaper. I intend to utilize my journalism experience to work towards a leadership career in advertising and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Note on A blogdown Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joewaynewright.github.io/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered an awesome tutorial on blogdown written by Alison. I have to admit this is the best blogdown tutorial I have seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Note on Two Beautiful Websites</title>
      <link>http://joewaynewright.github.io/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joewaynewright.github.io/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>To me, the two most impressive websites based on blogdown are:
 Rob J Hyndman&amp;rsquo;s personal website. Live Free or Dichotomize by Lucy and Nick et al.  I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
